coloradolottery.com 2012-05-23

# Colorado.gov: The Official State Web Portal: Privacy Statement

  * Colorado.gov Policies
  * Privacy Statement
    * Personal Information
    * Information Collected
    * Cookies
  * Security Statement
  * Accessibility Standards
  * Linking Policy
  * Supported Browsers

  * SERVICES
    * SERVICES

    * View All
  * HOW DO I?
    * HOW DO I?

    * View All
  * INFORMATION FOR
    * INFORMATION FOR

    * Senior Citizens
    * Citizens with Disabilities - Universal Access
    * Moving to Colorado
    * State Employees
    * Students
    * Staying Informed
    *  
  * STATE NEWS
    * STATE NEWS

    * Gov. Hickenlooper announces reinstatement of Energy and Mineral Impact Assistance grant program(May 22, 2012)
    * Lt. Gov. Garcia and Cabinet Secretary Garcia Sign Higher Education Tuition Reciprocity Agreement(May 22, 2012)
    * Lt. Gov. Garcia announces new Executive Director of Serve Colorado(May 22, 2012)
    * View All
  * ALERTS
    * ALERTS

    * Swine Flu Information
    *  
  * COMMUNITY HIGHLIGHT
    * **Description:** Scratch the veneer of the new-West look of urban Denver and you'll get a glimpse of the Old West, too. Sitting at 5,280 feet (one mile) above sea level...  

  * media center
    * WEB CAMS

  * governor
    * GOVERNOR

    * State Government
    * Local Government
    * Federal Government
    *  
  * CITIZEN ASSISTANCE
    * CITIZEN ASSISTANCE

    * Get Help
    * State Agencies and Indexes
    * Sign up for eNews
    *  
  * WEATHER
    * WEATHER

    * Denver/Centennial, CO  
A Few Clouds  
Temp 85.0 F (29.4 C)  
Humidity 9% 

  * TRAFFIC
    * TRAFFIC

    *  
  * colorful colorado
    * COLORFUL COLORADO

    * Send ePostcard

Snowmobiling at American Lakes

State Forest State Park, Colorado State Parks

## Privacy Statement

Thank you for visiting the Colorado home page and reviewing our Privacy Notice. This notice addresses collection, use of and access to information that may be obtained through use of the Colorado home page. This notice covers the following topics:

Personal Information

Information Collected  
Cookies
